{
    "0": {
        "question": "what feature collects company-specific data such as member status?",
        "answer": ["custom dimension"]
    },
    "1": {
        "question": "to recognize users across different devices, what feature must be enabled?",
        "answer": ["user id"]
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "in multi-channel funnel reports, how are default conversions credited?",
        "answer": ["equal credit along the conversion touchpoints"]
    },
    "3": {
        "question": "what report indicates the pages of a website where users first arrived?",
        "answer": ["landing pages report"]
    },
    "4": {
        "question": "what feature is required to send data from a web-connected device (like a point-of-sale system) to google analytics?",
        "answer": ["the measurement protocol"]
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "what is not considered a default \u201cmedium\u201d in google analytics?",
        "answer": ["google"]
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "what is the set of rules that determines how sales and conversions get credited based on touch-points in the conversion path?",
        "answer": ["attribution modeling"]
    },
    "7": {
        "question": "what data is google analytics goals unable to track?",
        "answer": ["customer\u2019s lifetime value"]
    },
    "8": {
        "question": "in custom reports, what must metrics and dimensions share in order to report accurately?",
        "answer": ["same scope"]
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "what is used to create smart goals?",
        "answer": ["machine-learning algorithms"]
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "which three campaign parameters are recommended to manually track campaigns?",
        "answer": ["medium, source, and campaign"]
    },
    "11": {
        "question": "filters cannot perform what action on collected data?",
        "answer": ["include shopping preferences"]
    },
    "12": {
        "question": "if a user watches a video with event tracking three times in a single session, analytics will count how many unique events?",
        "answer": ["1"]
    },
    "13": {
        "question": "what scope levels available for dimensions and metrics?",
        "answer": ["hit-level, session-level, product-level, or user-level scope"]
    },
    "14": {
        "question": "which assets cannot be shared in the solutions gallery?",
        "answer": ["custom dimensions"]
    },
    "15": {
        "question": "which goals are available in google analytics?",
        "answer": ["destination, event, duration, pages/screens per session"]
    },
    "16": {
        "question": "what report identifies browsers that may have had problems with a website?",
        "answer": ["the browser & os report"]
    },
    "17": {
        "question": "what scope would be set for a custom dimension that reports membership status for a customer rewards program?",
        "answer": ["user"]
    },
    "18": {
        "question": "what is not considered a \u201csource\u201d in google analytics by default?",
        "answer": ["email"]
    },
    "19": {
        "question": "if a user visits a web page with an embedded video, leaves without clicking on anything, and the session times out, how will google analytics report the session?",
        "answer": ["as a bounce"]
    },
    "20": {
        "question": "what is not a benefit of google analytics remarketing?",
        "answer": ["allow customers to quickly reorder an item they have previously purchased"]
    },
    "21": {
        "question": "what report provides data on how specific sections of a website performed?",
        "answer": ["content drilldown report"]
    },
    "22": {
        "question": "what criteria could not be used to create a dynamic remarketing audience?",
        "answer": ["users who returned an item they purchased"]
    },
    "23": {
        "question": "what report shows a visual representation of user interactions on a website?",
        "answer": ["behavior flow report"]
    },
    "24": {
        "question": "a new custom channel group may be applied retroactively to organize data that has been previously collected.",
        "answer": ["true"]
    },
    "25": {
        "question": "when linking a google ads account to google analytics, what is not possible?",
        "answer": ["adjust keyword bids in google ads from google analytics"]
    },
    "26": {
        "question": "what asset is used to build a remarketing list?",
        "answer": ["custom segment"]
    },
    "27": {
        "question": "if the google merchandise store sets up a url goal of \u201c/ordercomplete\u201d and a match type of \u201cbegins with\u201d, which of the following pages on www.googlemerchandisestore.com will not count as a goal?",
        "answer": ["/order/complete.php"]
    },
    "28": {
        "question": "what does assigning a value to a google analytics goal enable?",
        "answer": ["analyze a website conversion funnel', 'compare goal conversions and measure changes to a website', 'track real-time business revenue', 'track actual revenue from conversions"]
    },
    "29": {
        "question": "when does a default analytics session expire?",
        "answer": ["when a user is inactive on your website for more than 30 minutes"]
    },
    "30": {
        "question": "what report indicates the last page users viewed before leaving a website?",
        "answer": ["exit pages report"]
    },
    "31": {
        "question": "google analytics cannot collect data from which systems by default?",
        "answer": ["offline inventory database"]
    },
    "32": {
        "question": "what would prevent data from appearing in a custom report?",
        "answer": ["custom report isn\u2019t shared with users in the same view"]
    },
    "33": {
        "question": "where should the analytics tracking code be placed in the html of a webpage for data collection?",
        "answer": ["just before the closing </head> tag"]
    },
    "34": {
        "question": "segments will not allow you to do what?",
        "answer": ["permanently alter data"]
    },
    "35": {
        "question": "to recognize users across different devices, what is required for user id?",
        "answer": ["sign-in that generates and sets unique ids"]
    },
    "36": {
        "question": "what channel is not included in the default channels report?",
        "answer": ["device"]
    },
    "37": {
        "question": "what is not a filter setting for data in views?",
        "answer": ["restore"]
    },
    "38": {
        "question": "what feature can join offline business systems data with online data collected by google analytics?",
        "answer": ["data import"]
    },
    "39": {
        "question": "which reports indicate how website referrals, organic search, and ad campaigns assisted in conversions?",
        "answer": ["multi-channel funnel reports"]
    },
    "40": {
        "question": "in multi-channel funnel reports, what channel would not be credited with a conversion?",
        "answer": ["television commercials"]
    },
    "41": {
        "question": "if a destination goal is created for a newsletter sign-up and a user completes the newsletter sign-up three times in three separate sessions, how many goal conversions will google analytics count?",
        "answer": ["3"]
    },
    "42": {
        "question": "what is a \u201cdimension\u201d in google analytics?",
        "answer": ["an attribute of a data set that can be organized for better analysis."]
    },
    "43": {
        "question": "what feature is required to collect the number of comments users posted to a web page?",
        "answer": ["custom metric"]
    },
    "44": {
        "question": "which metric reports on how often a channel contributes to a conversion prior to last-click attribution?",
        "answer": ["assisted conversion"]
    },
    "45": {
        "question": "what is the \u201cbounce rate\u201d in google analytics?",
        "answer": ["the percentage of visits when a user landed on your website and exited without any interactions"]
    },
    "46": {
        "question": "what model represents the hierarchical structure of a google analytics account?",
        "answer": ["account > property > view"]
    },
    "47": {
        "question": "to increase the speed at which google analytics compiles reports, what action could be taken?",
        "answer": ["choose \u201cfaster response\u201d in the sampling pulldown menu"]
    },
    "48": {
        "question": "what campaign parameter is not available by default in google analytics ?",
        "answer": ["utm_adgroup"]
    },
    "49": {
        "question": "which kinds of hits does google analytics track?",
        "answer": ["all of the above"]
    },
    "50": {
        "question": "what\u00a0metric-dimension combination is\u00a0not valid?",
        "answer": ["sessions / bounce rate"]
    },
    "51": {
        "question": "which reports indicate how traffic arrived at a website?",
        "answer": ["all traffic"]
    },
    "52": {
        "question": "in views that don\u2019t have data import enabled, custom dimensions values may be viewed for dates before the custom dimension was created.",
        "answer": ["false"]
    },
    "53": {
        "question": "custom dimensions can be used as what?",
        "answer": ["all of the above"]
    },
    "54": {
        "question": "what feature must be enabled to use multi-channel funnels?",
        "answer": ["goals or ecommerce"]
    },
    "55": {
        "question": "what data table display compares report metrics to the website average?",
        "answer": ["comparison"]
    },
    "56": {
        "question": "view filters are applied in what order?",
        "answer": ["sequential order"]
    },
    "57": {
        "question": "auto-tagging is used to collect data from what kind of traffic?",
        "answer": ["google ads campaign traffic"]
    },
    "58": {
        "question": "what report indicates where users start or exit the conversion funnel?",
        "answer": ["goal flow report"]
    },
    "59": {
        "question": "which parameters can be included with an event hit for reporting?",
        "answer": ["category, action, label, value"]
    },
    "60": {
        "question": "what remarketing audiences cannot be defined by default?",
        "answer": ["users who visited a physical store"]
    },
    "61": {
        "question": "to track users and sessions across multiple domains, what first must be set up?",
        "answer": ["cross-domain tracking"]
    },
    "62": {
        "question": "when the same default tracking code is installed on pages with different domains, what will result?",
        "answer": ["analytics will associate users and sessions with their respective domains"]
    },
    "63": {
        "question": "what feature would be used to collect how many times users downloaded a product catalog?",
        "answer": ["event tracking"]
    },
    "64": {
        "question": "what is a \u201csecondary dimension\u201d in google analytics?",
        "answer": ["an additional report dimension for more specific analysis"]
    },
    "65": {
        "question": "when will google analytics be unable to identify sessions from the same user by default?",
        "answer": ["when the sessions happen in different browsers on the same device"]
    },
    "66": {
        "question": "what report shows which web pages get the most traffic and highest engagement?",
        "answer": ["all pages report"]
    },
    "67": {
        "question": "view filters may be applied retroactively to any data that has been processed.",
        "answer": ["false"]
    },
    "68": {
        "question": "what report shows the percentage of traffic that previously visited a website?",
        "answer": ["behavior > new vs returning report"]
    },
    "69": {
        "question": "once filters have been applied, what is the option to recover filtered data?",
        "answer": ["filtered data is not recoverable"]
    },
    "70": {
        "question": "for autotagging, what parameter does google ads include in the destination url?",
        "answer": ["gclid="]
    },
    "71": {
        "question": "what report shows the percent of site traffic that visited previously?",
        "answer": ["new vs returning report"]
    },
    "72": {
        "question": "what report shows users who initiated sessions over 1-day, 7-day, 14-day, and 30-day periods?",
        "answer": ["active users report"]
    },
    "73": {
        "question": "to view accurate data in a custom report, what action should be avoided?",
        "answer": ["pair metrics and dimensions of different scopes"]
    },
    "74": {
        "question": "how would a view filter be configured to include only users from brazil and argentina?",
        "answer": ["filter 1: include brazil or argentina"]
    },
    "75": {
        "question": "what cannot be collected by the default analytics tracking code?",
        "answer": ["user\u2019s favorite website"]
    },
    "76": {
        "question": "views can include website data collected before the view was created.",
        "answer": ["false"]
    },
    "77": {
        "question": "what report shows which types of mobile devices visited a website?",
        "answer": ["mobile > devices report"]
    },
    "78": {
        "question": "within how many days can a deleted view be restored?",
        "answer": ["35"]
    },
    "79": {
        "question": "what is not a benefit of using segments to analyze data?",
        "answer": ["permanently modify the data in a view"]
    },
    "80": {
        "question": "what type of custom report shows a static sortable table with rows of data?",
        "answer": ["flat table"]
    },
    "81": {
        "question": "what feature is required to track customer search terms on a website?",
        "answer": ["site search"]
    },
    "82": {
        "question": "what is a \u201cmetric\u201d in google analytics?",
        "answer": ["the numbers in a data set often paired with dimensions."]
    },
    "83": {
        "question": "what criteria cannot be used to create a custom segment?",
        "answer": ["ad type"]
    },
    "84": {
        "question": "which default traffic source dimensions does google analytics report for each website visitor?",
        "answer": ["source and medium"]
    },
    "85": {
        "question": "which user characteristic may not be used to change keyword bids in google ads?",
        "answer": ["ad preference"]
    },
    "86": {
        "question": "when does the analytics tracking code send a pageview hit to google analytics?",
        "answer": ["every time a user loads a webpage with embedded tracking code"]
    },
    "87": {
        "question": "what campaigns require manual tags on destination urls for tracking?",
        "answer": ["email campaigns"]
    },
    "88": {
        "question": "what filter would only include data from a campaign titled \u201cback to school\u201d in campaign reports?",
        "answer": ["custom include filter with field \u201ccampaign name\u201d and pattern \u201cback to school\u201d"]
    },
    "89": {
        "question": "what scope applies to custom metrics?",
        "answer": ["hit"]
    },
    "90": {
        "question": "what report compares metrics based on user acquisition date over a series of weeks?",
        "answer": ["cohort analysis"]
    },
    "91": {
        "question": "the default session timeout duration in google analytics is how many minutes?",
        "answer": ["30"]
    },
    "92": {
        "question": "what data does google analytics prohibit collecting?",
        "answer": ["personally identifable information"]
    },
    "93": {
        "question": "using a standard google analytics configuration, which characteristics cannot be used to create a custom segment?",
        "answer": ["users who are female and have children"]
    },
    "94": {
        "question": "sampling is applied to reports before segmentation.",
        "answer": ["false"]
    },
    "95": {
        "question": "if a web page visitor clears the analytics cookie from their browser, what will occur?",
        "answer": ["all of the above"]
    },
    "96": {
        "question": "which reports require the activation of advertising features?",
        "answer": ["demographics and interests reports"]
    },
    "97": {
        "question": "when does the tracking code send an event hit to google analytics?",
        "answer": ["every time a user performs an action with event tracking implemented"]
    },
    "98": {
        "question": "sharing a custom report will share the report configuration and data included in the report.",
        "answer": ["false"]
    },
    "99": {
        "question": "to collect how many times users downloaded a product catalog, what would you set up ?",
        "answer": ["event tracking"]
    },
    "100": {
        "question": "when will the analytics tracking code send a pageview hit to google analytics?",
        "answer": ["every time a user loads a webpage with embedded tracking code"]
    },
    "101": {
        "question": "what will happen if you install the same default tracking code on pages with different domains?",
        "answer": ["analytics will associate these users and sessions with a single domain"]
    },
    "102": {
        "question": "what will happen if a user clears the analytics cookie from their browser?",
        "answer": ["all of the above"]
    },
    "103": {
        "question": "which reports can show you how website referrals, organic search, and ad campaigns assisted in the conversion process?",
        "answer": ["multi-channel funnel reports"]
    },
    "104": {
        "question": "sharing a custom report will share the data in that report.",
        "answer": ["false"]
    },
    "105": {
        "question": "which user characteristic may not be used to change keyword bids in adwords?:",
        "answer": ["ad preference"]
    },
    "106": {
        "question": "what is required for user id to track users across different devices?",
        "answer": ["sign-in that generates and sets unique ids"]
    },
    "107": {
        "question": "by default, which of these is not considered a \u201cmedium\u201d in google analytics?",
        "answer": ["google"]
    },
    "108": {
        "question": "which reports require you to activate advertising features?",
        "answer": ["demographics and interests reports"]
    },
    "109": {
        "question": "assigning a value to a google analytics goal allows you to do which of the following?",
        "answer": ["compare goal conversions and measure changes and improvements to your site"]
    },
    "110": {
        "question": "which report shows users who initiated sessions over 1-day, 7-day, 14-day, and 30-day periods?",
        "answer": ["active users report', ':', 'the metrics in the active users report are relative to the last day in the date range you are using for the report.', 'read more here:"]
    },
    "111": {
        "question": "what scope would you apply for a custom dimension that collects data for users who log in to your website?",
        "answer": ["session', 'hit', 'product', 'user"]
    }
}
